SAIF ALI

FRONT END DEVELOPER | WEB DESIGNER UI UX DESIGNER | GRAPHICS DESIGNER



0300 0056887



livesaifali@gmail.com



Vip Gouri Town, Islamabad



Creative Web Designer, Front End Developer, UI UX Designer and Graphic Designer with innovative ideas and a unique approach to visuals. More than fours years of experience developing designs for print media, online websites, video, Graphics, User Experience Design, and advertising. Solid understanding of marketing principles and advertising techniques. Great attention to detail and a talent for creating memorable visual designs. Enthusiastic team player who is committed to delivering top results on time and within the budget. Passion for keeping clients satisfied with each project.

EDUCATION

2016 - 2020

BS / INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY SINDH AGRICULTURE UNIVERSITY 1ST DIVISION

TANDOJAM, HYDERABAD

2014 - 2016

INTERMEDIATE

BOARD OF INTERMEDIATE

B GRADE

SUKKUR, SINDH

CERTIFICATION

2021

DIGITAL MARKETING HUBSPOT ACADEMY

2021

IT FOR BUSINESS SUCCESS

HUBSPOT ACADEMY

2021

EFFECTIVE LEADERSHIP
HP LIFE FOUNDATION

2014

GRAPHICS DESIGNING

THE PUBLIC FORUM INSTITUTE

EXPERIENCE

FEB 2021 - PRESENT
IT SUPPORT OFFICER

STATE LIFE INSURANCE

ISLAMABAD

JAN 2020 - MAY 2020 SEO (SOFTWARE HOUSE) COMPUTER PLAZA ISLAMABAD



SKILLS

- FRONT END DEVELOPER
- WEB DESIGNER
- UI UX DESIGNER
- GRAPHICS DESIGNER
- DIGITAL MARKETING
- SEQ
- PHOTOGRAPHY
- COMMUNICATION

SOFTWARES

- PHOTOSHOP
- ILLUSTRATOR
- ADOBE XD
- FIGMA
- PREMIERE PRO
- AFTER EFFECTS
- LIGHTROOM
- MS OFFICE
- CORELDRAW

LANGUAGES

- ENGLISH
- URDU

REFERENCE

WILL BE AVAILABLE